<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Speedlab</string>
    <string name="lattice">Lattice</string>
    <string name="sirs"> SIRS-2 </string>
    <string name="ctest"> cTest </string>
    <string name="disp">Dispersal2</string>
    <string name ="vac">Vaccinated Communities</string>
    <string name ="dynamic">Dynamic Landscape</string>
    <string name ="frog">FrogSim</string>
    <string name="random">Random</string>
    <string name="startBtnTxt">Continue</string>
    <string name="stopBtnTxt">Pause</string>
    <string name="initBtnTxt">Start</string>
    <string name="restartBtnTxt">Restart</string>
    <string name="VaccCommModel"><b>Vaccinated Communites\n\n</b>Epidemiological model of a community-structured population with
        vaccination. Each column in the lattice image represents a different community.  Communities
        can have different vaccination levels.  Infected individuals contact others within their
        same community, or from among the entire population, to attempt infection. The probability
        of a contact being long-distance (not within one\'s own community) is given by \'alpha\'. If
        the target is susceptible and unvaccinated, it becomes infected. Susceptible vaccinated targets
        may or may not become infected, based on the given \'vaccine effectivess\' probability. Upon
        recovery, individuals become susceptible again at the given \'loss of resistance\' rate.</string>
        
    <string name="DynamicLandModel"><b>Dynamic Landscape\n\n</b>This is a population model where some efforts are being made
        to control the population.  For example, it might model the application of pesticides over
        a given landscape.  Pesticide is applied to blocks of sites, e.g. 3x4 blocks of sites at
        once (the block size is controlled by the two block size sliders). The overall per-site
        disturbance rate is held constant, even as the block size is changed. Pesticide is applied
        at the given \'disturbance rate\' per site; the pesticide dissipates and wears off at the
        specified \'regrowth rate\'. </string>
    <string name="VantsModel"><b>Vants\n\n</b>In a world consisting only of black and white tiles, there exist two types of
        creatures: Vants (virtual ants) and Antivants. At each time step a Vant steps forward onto a new tile and then makes a
        decision according to two simple rules:\nIf the new tile is white, the Vant colors the tile black and
        turns 90 degrees to the right.\nIf the new tile is black, the Vant colors the tile white and turns 90 degrees
        to the left.\nAntivants follow the same rules, except that they turn left instead of right and vice versa. This model
        demonstrates how very simple deterministic rules can result in extremely complex behavior.</string>
    <string name="RandomModel">Random model</string>
</resources>